Games

About

===============================================================================================================================================================================================

Games

About

* About

**Privacy Policy**
==================

### **Last Updated JANUARY 3, 2023**

We at Vector Unit respect your right to privacy.  This Privacy Policy explains how information is collected and utilized by Vector Unit, and how you can exercise your privacy rights.  This Privacy Policy applies to personal information that we collect through our mobile, PC and console **Games**, and at our **Website** at [www.vectorunit.com](http://www.vectorunit.com/) (together, “**Services**”).

If after reading this you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or your personal information, please send an email to [info@vectorunit.com](mailto:info@vectorunit.com) and we will try to address it.

**What personal information does Vector Unit collect and why?**
---------------------------------------------------------------

Vector Unit is a gaming company, headquartered in California, in the United States of America.   Our main business is to develop and publish game applications online via distribution networks like Apple iTunes or Steam.  For more information about Vector Unit, please see the [About Us](http://www.vectorunit.com/company/) section of our Website.

The personal information that we may collect about you through the Services broadly falls into the following categories:  When you play our Games or visit our Website, we may collect certain information automatically from your device; this information may be considered personal information under applicable data protection laws.  Also from time to time, you may send us personal information voluntarily, for example when you email us for support.

### Information that we collect automatically in our Games

We automatically collect certain types of anonymous information when you interact with some of our Games, via a 3rd party analytics partner such as [Flurry](http://www.flurry.com/).  This information is stored in our partner's servers, and visible to us in aggregated or pseudonymized form which does not focus on you individually.

Specifically, this may include information like your device type, unique device identification numbers, broad geographic location (e.g. country derived from IP address) and technical information such as crash reporting.  In addition, we may collect information about your interactions with our Games, such as how long you play for, or whether you've encountered any technical glitches.

This type of anonymized data enables us to figure out how players use our Games, so we can make improvements to our Games over time, such as fixing bugs or identifying areas of the game which are too difficult.

In addition, in some of our free to play games we also partner with mobile advertising networks, such as [AdColony](https://www.adcolony.com/).  Each of these companies collect some pseudonymized usage data from players, such as whether or not a player finishes watching an ad all the way through, or whether or not a user clicks on an ad.  

For information about exercising your data rights with our 3rd party partners, please see **Contacting our partners** below.

**Apple Arcade**

Please note that the Apple Arcade version of our games does not collect any of the above mentioned information from your device. The single exception is for multiplayer: we read your Game Center gamer ID and gamertag in order to connect you with other players and post to leaderboards. Aside from that, no data is collected, stored, or transmitted.

### Information that we collect automatically on our Website

Our website is hosted by [Squarespace](https://www.squarespace.com/), which uses cookies and similar tracking technology (collectively, “**Cookies**”) to collect and use personal information about you.  For further information about the types of Cookies used by Squarespace, why, and how you can control Cookies, please see the [Squarespace Cookie Notice](https://www.squarespace.com/cookie-policy).

When you visit our Website, the information Squarespace collects automatically may include information like your IP address, device or browser type, unique device identification numbers, or broad geographic location (e.g. country).  This information is stored in our partner's servers, and visible to us in anonymous, aggregated or pseudonymized form which does not focus on you individually.

Viewing this information enables us to better understand the people who visit our Website, where they come from, and what content is of interest to them so we can improve the quality and relevance of our Website to our visitors.

For information about exercising your data rights with our 3rd party partners, please see **Contacting our partners** below.

### Information that you provide voluntarily for authentication

Some of our games offer **Platform Services** which enable you to connect to other users or back up your save file online.  For example, you might log into iCloud on an iOS device, or Google Play Games Services on an Android device.  In such cases, we may get access to some information such as your Username or Gamertag. In such cases, we treat such information in accordance to the privacy mandates of the Platform Service, and of this Privacy Policy.

For information about exercising your data rights with our 3rd party partners, please see **Contacting our partners** below.

### Information that you provide voluntarily for communication

Certain other parts of our Services may ask you to provide personal information voluntarily.  For example, when you sign up for our mailing list, we may ask you to provide your name and email address, or receive that information when you send us a support email.  The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide it.

At any time you wish to access, correct, update or request deletion of your personal information, you may do so.  Please see **Your Data Subject Rights (DSRs)** below.

Legal basis for processing personal information
-----------------------------------------------

Our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described above will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it.

However, we will normally collect personal information from you only (i) where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you, (ii) where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your rights, or (iii) where we have your consent to do so.

If we ask you to provide personal information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contact with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your personal information is mandatory or not (as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your personal information).

We will process your information for the purposes of operating our Website, Games and other Services and communicating with you as necessary for those purposes and in our legitimate commercial interests, for instance, when responding to your queries, undertaking marketing activities, improving our Games, Website and other Services or for the purposes of detecting or preventing illegal activities.

Who does Vector Unit share my personal information with?
--------------------------------------------------------

Generally speaking, we're in the business of making games, not sharing or selling data.  We take pains to protect your data and ensure that whatever data you share with us is used strictly for the purposes of improving our Services, and for staying in touch with our players and Website visitors.

However, we may disclose your personal information to the following categories of recipients:

* to **third party services providers** and partners who provide data processing services to us, or who otherwise process personal information for purposes that are described in this Privacy Policy.  See **Contacting our partners** below.

* to **any competent law enforcement body**, regulatory, government agency, court or other third party where we believe disclosure is necessary (i) as a matter of applicable law or regulation, (ii) to exercise, establish or defend our legal rights, or (iii) to protect your vital interests or those of any other person;
    
* to a **potential or actual buyer** (and its agents and advisers) in connection with any proposed or actual purchase, merger or acquisition of any part of our business, provided that we inform the buyer it must use your personal information only for the purposes disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

**How does Vector Unit keep my personal information secure?**
-------------------------------------------------------------

We use appropriate technical and organisational measures designed to protect the personal information that we collect and process about you.  The measures we use are designed to provide a level of security appropriate to the risk of processing your personal information.

Whenever possible the information we collect is anonymized, hashed, pseudonymized, or otherwise obscured, so that the information viewed is not linked to any identifiable individual by the person viewing it.  

We limit access to all personal information, including such pseudonymized information, to individuals within the company who require that access (for example, tech support personnel, or analytics staff) and who have been trained on our privacy policies.

**International data transfers**
--------------------------------

Your personal information may be transferred to, and processed in, countries other than the country in which you are a resident.  These countries may have data protection laws that are different from the laws of your country.

Specifically, our servers are located in the United States, and our third party service providers and partners operate around the world.  This means that when we collect your personal information we may process it in any of these countries.

However, we have taken appropriate safeguards to require that your personal information will remain protected in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Data retention
--------------

We retain personal information we collect from you where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, to provide you with a service you have requested or to comply with applicable legal, tax or accounting requirements).

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymise it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

Children
--------

Our Services are intended for general audiences and Vector Unit does not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children.

If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [info@vectorunit.com](mailto:info@vectorunit.com). We will delete such information from our files within a reasonable period of time.

Your Data Subject Rights (DSRs)
-------------------------------

We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their Data Subject Rights (DSRs) in accordance with applicable data protection laws.  When applicable, we will fulfil your requests ourselves. In the case of data which we do not directly maintain or store, we will refer you to the appropriate partner to fulfill your request.  For information about exercising your DSRs with our 3rd party partners, please see **Contacting our partners** below.

You have the following Data Subject Rights:

* If you wish to **access, correct, update or request deletion** of your personal information, you can do so at any time by using the contact details provided under the “How to contact us” heading below.
    
* In addition, you can **object to processing** of your personal information, ask us to **restrict processing** of your personal information or request portability of your personal information. Again, you can exercise these rights by contacting us using the contact details provided under the “How to contact us” heading below.
    
* You have the right to **opt-out of marketing communications** we send you at any time.  You can exercise this right by clicking on the “unsubscribe” or “opt-out” link in the marketing e-mails we send you.  
    
* Similarly, if we have collected and process your personal information with your consent, then you can **withdraw your consent** at any time.  Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
    
* You have the **right to complain to a data protection authority** about our collection and use of your personal information.  For more information, please contact your local data protection authority.

Contacting our partners
-----------------------

We use 3rd party software and services for event tracking, advertising, game services, and other types of functionality.  Each of our Services is different, and not all of these partners are applicable to all of our Services. If you wish to exercise your data rights and are unsure of whom to contact, please email us at [info@vectorunit.com](mailto:info@vectorunit.com) and we will assist you.

### Mobile Analytics / Ad Networks

* **Game Analytics**

    * DSR Contact: [privacy@gameanalytics.com](mailto:privacy@gameanalytics.com)
        
* **AdColony**

    * Send DSR requests to: [privacy@adcolony.com](mailto:privacy@adcolony.com)
        
* **Yahoo Flurry Analytics**
    
    * [Privacy Policy](https://policies.oath.com/us/en/oath/privacy/index.html) (covered by Flurry's Parent company Oath)

### Platform Services

* **Apple Services** (Game Center, iCloud, etc.)
    
    * See Apple's guide [Here's how to manage your privacy](https://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/)
        
* **Google Play Services** (Google Play Games, Drive, etc.)
    
    * See Google's [Personal info & privacy](https://myaccount.google.com/intro/privacy) dashboard
        
* **Amazon Services** (Game Circle, Whispersync, etc.)
    
    * Amazon's [Privacy Policy](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496)

### Website

* **Squarespace**

    * Send DSR requests to:  [privacy@squarespace.com](mailto:privacy@squarespace.com)

Updates to this Privacy Policy
------------------------------

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time in response to changing legal, technical or business developments. When we update our Privacy Policy, we will take appropriate measures to inform you, consistent with the significance of the changes we make.  

How to contact us
-----------------

If you have any questions or concerns about our use of your personal information, please contact us at [info@vectorunit.com](mailto:info@vectorunit.com).

This work is licensed under a [Creative Commons License.](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/3.0/)
